and why for 8 years
а почему в течение 8ми лет
uh I can't say that all but
ээ не могу утверждать что всеми но
probably the majority of the majority of the
наверное большинства большинством
residents of the LNR DNR supported all this For
жителей лнр ДНР это всё поддерживалось С
what purpose uh so good A look U
какой целью э так хорошо А смотри Э ты
can you tell me how many people fled from the
можешь сказать сколько людей убежала из
LNR DNR so
лнр д лнр так
Invited No I can't tell you that
Званого Нет я не могу вам на это
reply
ответить
here Hello Good
вот Привет Добрый
day How are you doing normally I ask people from
день Как дела нормально Я у людей из
Russia how do you feel about the
России спрашиваю как вы относитесь к
war in
войне в
Ukraine I think
Украине считаю
it was inevitable sooner or later
что это было неизбежным рано или поздно
And why Well that is you support how
А почему Ну то есть ты поддер как
inevitable inevitably you support you
неизбежно неизбежно ты поддерживаешь ты
say correctly that they brought troops into
говоришь правильно что вели войска в
Ukraine I  I think that it was necessary to
Украину Я считаю что требовалось
comply with the Minsk agreements, according to which
соблюдение минских соглашений по котором
they would have remained part of Ukraine. Wait, do you think it is right to send troops to Ukraine or is it wrong? And why was it inevitable? Well, explain. Well, why was it inevitable? According to the Minsk agreements, the territories of the LPR and the DPR would have
соглашениям территории лн ДНР они бы
remained part of Ukraine. No.
остались в составе Украины Не так
is that so But why were these agreements not
ли Но почему эти соглашения не
observed unilaterally
соблюдались в одностороннем порядке
and because of this it was simply
и ввиду этого людям уже было просто
impossible for people to live and now they have made it
невозможно жить и теперь сделали чтобы
impossible for them at all for
им вообще было невозможно чтобы там
military actions to take place there
военные действия были дат
subsequently it will be possible to live And you
в последующем будет возможно жить И вам
too will be able to live like this wait
тоже будет возможно жить так подожди ещё
again I didn't understand that is because the
раз я не понял то есть из-за того что не
Minsk agreements were not implemented
исполнялись минские соглашения просто не
some agreements were simply not implemented Russia
исполнялись какие-то соглашения Россия
bombed this It's not just an agreement
разбомбил это Это не просто соглашение
so so Well
так так Ну а
what According to the Minsk  agreements
что Согласно же минским соглашениям
territory of the LPR LPR they would have remained
территория лнр лнр они бы остались в
part of Ukraine so and so But why were these
составе Украины так и и Но а почему эти
agreements not observed Why did
соглашения не соблюдались Почему 8 лет
they kill civilians for 8 years stop stop stop 8
убивали мирные граждане стоп стоп стоп 8
years of killing where did you get such 8 years of
лет убивали откуда у вас такая 8 лет
killing with civilians Where did you get such
убивали с мирные граждане Откуда такая
information and then who led Wait  wait,
информация а то кто вёл Подожди подожди
where did 8 years go, how many civilians were killed,
э откуда 8 лет сколько убито граждан
for example, last year, here is the
например мирных в прошлом году вот
twenty-first year, for the twenty-first year,
двадцать первый год за дцать первый год
I can say that for the entire time there are
я могу сказать что за всё время там
more than 7,000. It seems no, no, you are
больше 7.000 Вроде нет нет это вы
lying. Why am I lying, you
обманываете Почему я обманываю
are lying. Where did you get this
обманываете А откуда у вас это такие
data about 7,000?  Well here's from Wikipedia from
данные про 7.000 Ну вот из Википедия из
Wikipedia But
Википедии А
here's the official what-you say is different
вот официальное что-ты говорят другое
really
правда
officially for example here's a report Well also
официально например вот отч да Ну также
obs e Now look let's talk
обс е Теперь смотрите давайте давайте
about the atom  so I understood that if you don't
про ато так я понял что если вы не
want to listen to me I can just not
хотите меня слушать я могу просто вас не
you let's you didn't want to listen to me I
я давайте вы меня не хотели слушать Я
say you interrupt me we interrupted each other
говорю вы меня перебивайте мы друг друга
let's listen to the end oh no you're
перебивали давайте дослушай а ну нет вы
interrupting me for some reason According to you
перебивается почему-то Согласно вы
just touched on the issue They said  that
сейчас прос затронули Они же сказали что
they were performing espionage functions, this is
они выполняли функции шпионажа это же
not even said on our news, stop, but there
даже не по нашим новостям говорят стоп а
were no Russians in the
русских не было в составе
OSCE, Russians were there, but the Russians
обсе россияне там были но россияне
were performing their function of espionage, no. That
выполняли свою функцию шпионажа нет А то
is, all the others were performing the function of
есть все остальные исполняли функцию
espionage, but the Russians, no, I can’t
шпионажа а россияне не я не могу
say that and single out one in particular
так говорить выделять конкретно одного
just in general I looked at the Spanish
просто в целом Я смотрел испанский
source and it was said there
источник и Там говорилось об этом
Spanish source Spanish source Yes
испанский источник испанский источник Да
and what is the Spanish source Now I am
а что за испанский источник Сейчас я вам
correcting you No no just tell me what is the
правлю Да не не просто скажи что за
Spanish source what is it there
испанский источник что это там
Eh it is a Spanish newspaper
Ээ это испанская газета
Varya that is a Spanish newspaper It is a
Варя то есть испанская газета Есть
reliable source  about what
достоверным источником про то что
is happening here in Ukraine, so
происходит тут в Украине так
reliability is generally objective, that
достоверность она в целом объективна то
is, one cannot consider some information
есть нельзя считать какую-то информацию
completely reliable.
полностью достоверной по ская
reliability is generally objective,
достоверность она в целом объективна
something I did not understand. Well, in general, let's say
что-то Я не понял Ну в целом допустим
Take Okay, in short, look, I got it. In
Взять Ладно короче смотри я понял В
general, about Spanish. I just didn't understand
общем про испанский Я просто не понял
why Spanish is the source. No, it's
почему испанский именно источник Нет ну
just that it's a
просто как
custom. Russians don't believe
бы уже такой обычай россияне не верят
what they say in Ukraine, but in Ukraine they
тому что говорят в Украине а в Украине
believe what they say. In Russia, you can
верят тому что говорят в России можно
look at the third side. That's the
посмотреть третью сторону Вот именно
Spanish one.  newspaper so if in a
испанскую газету так вот если в
Spanish newspaper they wrote then it's a
испанской газете написали Значит это
sure thing yes no no but I just
верняк да нет нет но просто я в этой это
didn't notice it in this one but you look you yourself from
не замечал а вот ты смотри ты сам с
what region of Russia am I from the center Well the
какого региона России я с центра Ну
center is different the center is Well the center of
центр это разный центр есть Ну центр
Russia Moscow itself Moscow Yes here I am
России Москва самой Москвы Да вот я
I see that you from Moscow understand very well
смотрю ты с Москвы очень так хорошо
what is happening here in
разбираешься что тут происходит в
Ukraine yes that is you follow
Украине да то есть Ты следишь за
Ukrainian politics Well, no I
политикой украинской Так ну не по не
can't say that I follow it directly but
могу сказать что прямо слежу но новости
your news Your news Yes I read And for example
ваши Ваши новости Да Читаю А например за
you follow Russian politics I will
российской политикой Ты следишь
say Yes and who is the chairman
скажу Да а кто председатель
State Duma of the Russian
Государственной Думы Российской
Federation - Volodin is correct and
Федерации - Володин правильно а
uh
э
this how is it in Russian government Who
этот как это по-русски правительство Кто
heads your uh Government of the
возглавляет ваше ээ Правительство
Russian Federation I'm afraid to
Российской Федерации Боюсь сейчас
make a mistake now
ошибиться
Uh this is not Mishustin in this case it seems like Mishustin
Ээ это не Мишустин случае вроде Мишустин
I just didn't understand exactly it seems like Mishustin O
я вот точно не понял вроде Мишустин О
you see Well, at least you know your way around Well,
видишь Хорошо хоть ориентируешься Да
because usually there are a bunch of people there who
потому что обычно куча люди которые там
will tell us something about Ukraine, they don’t
нам что-то про Украину расскажет они не
know what’s going on in Russia at the top
знаю что у них в России там в топе
Well, okay, let’s talk about you, you’re an expert,
делается Ну хорошо давай вот ты эксперт
we can talk further No, I’m not an expert I’m an
можно поговорить дальше Да не Эксперт Я
ordinary citizen Well, well, No, well  you in terms of
обычный житель Ну вот Не ну ты в плане
as a citizen of yours Do you at least
как свой гражданин Ты хотя бы
understand what is going on at the top of your
разбираешься что у тебя в верхушке
politics because many do not
политики делается потому что многие не
understand it so Okay Look, I'll
понимают этого так Окей Вот смотри а я
ask you now What channel should I
сечас спрошу На каком себя канале
watch later Andrey popk Andrey pok
смотреть потом Андрей попк Андрей пок
Andrey I'll write to you now Yes, come on
Андрей я те сейчас напишу Да давай сыл
[  music]
[музыка]
right away let's talk about ato now
сразу вот давай поговорим теперь про ато
Because you said ato can you
Потому что ты сказал ато ты можешь
name the date when
назвать Дату когда началось
ato started Now I'll find you right away no no like
ато Сейчас я тебе сразу найду нене вот
that without finding And you'll find the channel
так без нахождения А ты канал найдёшь
you mean Yes I'm looking for a channel on tube on youtube
имеешь виду Да я канал на тубе на юбе же
on youtube Yes
искать на юбе Да
[  music]
[музыка]
now it's loaded for me in a second,
сейчас секунду у меня
but I'm
а
afraid to be wrong, it was April
то боюсь быть неверным это был апрель
2014. Absolutely right, if you
2014 года Абсолютно верно если точно
look exactly, yes, then April 14th.
смотреть да то 14 апреля так
2014 So when did
2014 года Так а когда ээ в на Донбассе
armed hostilities begin in Donbass, Donetsk region? I
Донецкой области начались вооружённые
can’t say, but I can say 2 days
Э не смо а я могу сказать на 2 дня
earlier, on April 12, 2014, an
раньше так 12 апреля 2014 года
employee of the Russian FSB, Igor Strelkov,
работник российского ФСБ Игорь стрелков
aka Igor Girkin,
он же Игорь гиркин так с вооружённым
entered from Russian territory with an armed detachment and
отрядом с территории России зашёл и
captured  police department in Slavyansk
захватил отделение полиции в Славянске
So that's how the armed
Так с этого и началось вооружённая
resistance began, that is, only 2 days later the
сопротивление так то есть через 2 дня
ATO began. So on the evening of the
только началось ато Вот вечером
twelfth they signed a decree
двенадцатого числа подписали указ тогда
about the ATO and on the fourteenth it
про ато и четырнадцатого числа оно
began and so it turns out that these
началось так и получается вот эти
militants from Russia were driving like that, this
боевики с России так ехали вот этот
motor there and a bunch more  there are people there, that is, it
там моторо ещ куча там народу то есть
turns out that before the
получается до прихода
Russians arrived we had no war, so it
русских никакой войны у нас не было так
turns out that the Russians started
то есть получается русские развязали
the war, then the Russians supported this
войну потом русские поддерживали эту
war for 8 years, and now the Russians are doing the
войну 8 лет так и теперь русские делают
third phase, and Ukraine is to blame.
третью фазу а виновата
If you watch the interview of
Украина Вот ты если посмотри интервью
this Girkin Gordon, where he directly
этого гиркина Гордона где он прямо
says  how did he start a war
рассказывает как что он развязал войну
Yes in Slavyansk  came in okay then uh I
Да в Славянск зашёл ладно тогда ээ Я как
understand now there were no questions for me
понял сейчас никаких вопросов ко мне не
this is now found by the story from
было это сейчас нашло повествование от
you And then such a question And why
вас А тогда такой вопрос А почему в
for 8 years
течение 8ми лет
uh I can't say that all but
ээ не могу утверждать что всеми но
probably the majority of the majority of the
наверное большинства большинством
residents of the LNR DNR all this was supported For
жителей лнр ДНР это всё поддерживалось С
what purpose uh  so good And look E
какой целью э так хорошо А смотри Э ты
can you tell me how many people fled from
можешь сказать сколько людей убежало из
the LPR to the LPR so
лнр до лнр так
Zvanogo No I can't answer you on that
Званого Нет я не могу вам на это
Look That is it turns out that
ответить Вот смотри То есть получается
for some reason a lot of people fled
очень много людей почему-то перебежала
to the territory controlled by Ukraine
на под контрольную Украине территорию
so but they also fled to the
так но также перебежали же и на
territory  directly to the Russian
территорию непосредственно российской
Federation Russian Yes, that's right, I
Феде российской Да правильно вот я вчера
was talking to a guy yesterday, he's 18 years old I say,
с парнем общался ему 18 лет Я говорю А
Why did you end up in Russia, he says,
почему ты вот попал в Россию говорит
because I was 10 years old, my mother ran away from the war
потому что мне было 10 лет мама от войны
here I say, why, Because it
перебежала сюда Я кажу а почему Потому
was territorially closer and there
что территориально было ближе и там
were relatives there, so  that is, people
родственники были так то есть люди
ran to where there were some connections
перебегали туда где были какие-то связи
Well, well, probably the same thing ran to Ukraine
Так ну вот Наверное в Украину тоже самое
because Well, why didn't they
перебегали потому Да ну почему они не
stay, why don't they return to the
остались почему они не возвращаются в
DPR
ДНР
LPR Well, I think that,
лнр Ну я считаю что
let's say, having  acquaintances who are in
допустим имея знакомых которые прот на
that territory some stayed,
той территории некоторые остались
let's say, for the reasons that there were
допустим по причинам того что были
sick streaks or there was no financial
больные стрики либо не было финансовой
opportunity or they simply did not want to
возможности либо просто не хотели
leave their homeland. And for example, do you know
покидать родину А например тебе известно
what a prison is,
что такое тюрьма
isolation? I'm talking about this prison, a prison at
изоляция мне про эту тюрму тюрьму в
the airport, let's say, no, no, look, there
аэропорту допустим не не вот смотри вот
is a prison.  isolation so that is very
есть тюрьма изоляция так то есть очень
Look how all the unwanted are tortured there
Посмотри как там всех неугодных и пытают
and what kind of torture takes place there so
и какие пытки там происходят так вот
there is an exchange here a guy uh who was
есть по обмену вот парень ээ который был
in this prison then he was released He
в этой тюрьме потом его освободили Он
even wrote a book about it so that is how do
книжку про это написал даже так то есть
you think you can be in here in  in this
как ты считаешь можно быть в вот в этом
DPR so now this is what will happen to the person
ДНР так сейчас вот что будет с человеком
who says I am for Ukraine what
который скажет я за Украину что с ним
will happen to him I don't know what will happen to him honestly
будет Я не знаю что с ним будет честно
I just can't even say objectively
просто я даже не могу объективно сказать
because I don't have any information
потому что у меня нет никакой информации
That's it and now you say Why do
Вот вот а а теперь ты говоришь А почему
people  from the DPR they kind of support And you
люди из ДНР как бы поддерживают А ты
try and try not to support when there are
попробуй попробуй не поддержать когда у
machine gunners near your house, so to speak
тебя под домом автоматчики
Well, now I
Ну сейчас
would like to ask a little bit another question,
немножко хотел бы вот другую вопрос
not just let's finish with this
задать не вот просто давай вот с этим
first Yes, do people think they can do
сначала закончим Да счи люди могут
their own thing
свою ль
if for this they can
если за это им может
be sentenced to death there is the death penalty By the way I
быть там смертная казнь есть Кстати я
know that in the DPR there is the death penalty but
знаю что в ДНР есть смертная казнь но
again I for 8 years despite
опять же я вот за за 8 лет несмотря на
my young age and although I read many sources
мой юный возраст и хоть много источников
I have never heard about
читаю я ни разу не слышал про то чтобы
someone for  that they don't agree,
кого-то за то что они не соглас просто
people just disappear, it's true, without any trial, and
люди пропадают правда Без всякого суда и
that disappears, well, I, I, I don't, I don't care
то что пропадает Ну я я я не я не уче ра
what this is, no, I say that I haven't heard
что этого Нет я говорю что я не слышал
about this, well, it disappeared, and that's it, and no one
об этом Ну а так пропал И всё И никто не
hears, and so I do too,  watched Voikov e
слышат Да также я вот смотрел Войков э
from Mariupol Well, war correspondents are
из Мариуполя Ну военкоры - это
propagandists Well, that is, there is no
пропагандисты Ну то есть их не имеет
point in watching them now if you want an
смысла смотреть сейчас если ты хочешь
objective I ask for forgiveness
объективную прошу прошу прощения
so I ask for forgiveness not for long I just
так Прошу прощения не надолго Мне просто
need to go now there
нужно сейчас идти
will be war correspondents in the sense that they are not so
будет военкоры в плане они не такие
widespread Well, don't write In general, no  Well,
массовые Ну не распи В общем не Ну
look, a war correspondent is someone who is allowed
смотри военкор - это тот кого пускают
there by the military, so he
военные туда так он
won't be able to say anything wrong
что-то скажем неправильное не сможет
because he'll say, "Listen, dude,
сказать потому что скажет слухай чувак
don't go there or anything." The point is that
всё не лезь сюда не там
he's not the one speaking.  there were just
Суть в том что не он говорит просто были
interviews with residents of Mariupol who
интервью с жителями Мариуполя которые
talked about the same prison, only
рассказывали о такой же тюрьме только
it was organized by the SBU, again, as I
она была организована СБУ опять же как я
said before, one cannot assert the
до этого говорил нельзя утверждать о
reliability of any information in
достоверности какой-либо информации в
[music]
[музыка]
in general, but they also talked about torture and about the
целом но они говорили тоже о пытках и о
fact that people used to  disappeared
том то что люди бывало пропадали
accordingly That is, did I understand correctly
соответственно То есть я правильно понял
that people are now in Mariu so when
что люди сейчас вот в мариу так когда
Russian troops came there so they
туда пришли войска русские так они это
say this in the presence of Russian troops
говорят в присутствии российских войск
so no no there are no military at all well
так нет нет там военных вообще нет ну
how are they not in Mariupol No I
как нету в Мариуполь Нет я имею в
mean behind the scenes no yes but now
виду за кадром нету да но сейчас
a little bit Yes I don't have a question whether they ate behind
немножко Да я вопрос не пол ели они за
the scenes or whether they ate at all yes that is
кадром или ели они вообще да то есть
look what let's say let's do it this way in
смотри что скажем так давайте так в
Russia in Russia in peaceful Russia a
России вот в России в мирной России
person can speak out freely so
человек может свободно высказываться
that he won't be taken to the police can he
чтобы его не забрали в полицию может он
go to a rally and something  say something
выйти на митинг и что-то сказать такое
that the authorities won't
что власти не
like Well, there are examples when
понравится Ну есть примеры когда это
you could say this, there are those when you got into trouble,
могли вы сказывать есть когда попадали
yes, well, most, that is, they won't say it and
да да ну большинство то есть не скажут и
many are afraid, they say I won't go out because the
многие боятся говорят я не выйду потому
police will immediately grab me So this is
что меня сразу загребу в полицию Так это
in peaceful Russia, and what will happen  with a
вроде в мирной там России а что будет с
person in occupied Mariupol
человеком в оккупированном Мариуполе
if he now comes out and says you are for
если он сейчас вот выйдет и скажет ти за
Ukraine What will happen to him a little bit well let's
Украину Что будет с ним немножко ну
move away from what I was saying I was
отошли от того что я рассказывал Я же
saying that the person is not alone A
рассказывал про то что человек э не один
civilian without the
Гражданский житель без ээ там
presence of people with weapons was saying
присутствие людей с оружием рассказывал
that  there was such a thing and not again I
о том что там такое было и не ещё раз я
I am saying here are people who look
Я же говорю вот люди которые смотрите
there is an occupation going on there now so that is
там сейчас ходится оккупация так то есть
there is martial law there essentially so that
там там военное положение по сути так то
is there is no any right or
есть там нету никакого ни ээ права ни
legal that is they can come and take you
юридическое то есть могут прийти тебя
away and everything is so that is  no why is there a
забрать и всё так то есть нет почему
military administration as far as I know
военная администрация насколько я знаю
Well that's right Well look I mean
есть Ну правильно Ну смотри имею в виду
if we said that in Ukraine about
вот если мы в Украине так сказали о
the legal
юридическом
Well what kind of judicial system is there there uh that is there is a
Ну ну а какие там ээ то есть там
human rights Yes
судебная система есть права человека Да
uh essentially when the military
ээ по сути когда приходит военая
administration comes Yes there is one
администрация Да есть ведь она же
is also a temporarily acting
является временно действующим органом
authority Don't look That is, you think
власти Не смотрите То есть вы считаете
that for example on the territory there DPR LPR
что например на территории там ДНР лнр
now this is controlled there are
сейчас вот это контролируемая есть
human rights are observed so Freedom of
соблюдаются права человека так Свобода
speech
высказываний
I don't know about this That's the
Я не знаю об этом Вот вот в том-то и
point that is  look it turns out that
дело то есть смотрите получается так как
you most likely don't know,
вы скорее всего не знаете вот да
look, could I or you
смотрите Смог ли я или вы свободно
speak freely in the occupied
высказываться на оккупированной
territory, not the way the occupiers want?
территории не так как хочется оккупантам
Could you do
Смогли бы вы
that? The question is, if people didn't want to
так вопрос в том Если бы люди не хотели
share it, they wouldn't
этим делиться они бы не стали бы этим
share it. Here you are  could have said something
делиться Вот вы бы могли сказать чтото
wrong under Stalin people who
не так вот при Сталине люди которые
e I think that well knowing myself If I was
э Я думаю что ну зная себя Если бы меня
not satisfied with something even at the risk of
бы что-то не устраивало даже под риском
taking my life I could have
того что я лишуй жизнь Я бы мог бы
said something maybe yes But many
что-то высказать может да А много не
can't  under Stalin, here's what you
могут вот при Сталине вот Как вы
think now, there was just a question
считаете сейчас сейчас был просто вопрос
specifically addressed to me, I
Конкретно адресованный мне я на него
answered it. Unfortunately, I have to go and
ответил Я мне к сожалению нужно идти и
our business is interrupted, but it was
наш дело этом прерывается но было
nice to talk to you. Have a nice
приятно с вами побеседовать Хорошего вам
day.
дня
Think about whether people under
Подумайте над тем или могут люди в
occupation can freely express what they say.  not
оккупации свободно высказывать то что не
as if it does not correspond to the occupation
как бы не соответствует оккупационный
authorities safely just we we started to
властям безопасно просто мы мы начали
talk about one thing finished about another it is
говорить за одно закончили за дру оно
connected it is very connected yes that is it is
связано оно очень связано да то есть оно
not connected you you referred to the fact
не связано ве не вы вы сослались на то
that here people were talking and We
что вот люди говорили и Мы
switched Is there Freedom of expression they were talking
перешли Есть ли Свобода высказы говорили
but we  at all  they started talking about prisons
но мы вообще начали говорить про тюрмы
from Mariupol and now they are talking about the fact
из Мариуполя и сечас жели говорить за то
that it is impossible to speak out about anything else.
что нельзя о чём-то другом
So, on the territory of still
высказываться Значит на территории ещ
As you say, not occupied, not
Как вы говорите Не оккупированного не
occupied Mariupol, then it
оккупированного Мариуполя значит там
was also impossible to speak out there. If
тоже нельзя было что-то высказывать Если
people were simply taken away and where they were simply taken
людей просто так увозили а где возили
so from Mariupol there was bad so people did
так из Мариуполя там было пло так люди
not leave so they tell us that
не уезжали так вот нам говорят что
now there are a lot of refugees in Russia so
сейчас куча беженцев в Россию так
they fled from the Nazi regime And who
убежали от нацистского режима А кто
forbade leaving Mariupol they
запрещал из Мариуполя уезжать спокойно
went calmly everything was fine people
ездили всё нормально люди
lived it's just that when we talk about
жили вот просто когда мы говорим про
Mariupol Ukrainian legislation was in effect there
Мариуполь там действовало украинское
everything was fine  yes And on the
законодательство всё нормально да А на
territory of the DPR what is
территории ДНР что
in effect no if we are talking
действует нет вот если мы сейчас говорим
about a prison now even now photographs
вот о тюрьме даже вот сейчас фотографии
I don't know how bad it is for you probably you ca
Я не знаю насколько вам наверно плохо се
n't see it well now I'll try even if I could see a
плохо видно сечас Я постараюсь даже если
photograph I
было видно мне фотография Просто я тоже
can just show some kind of photograph it's
какую-то Фотографию могу показать она
nothing  won't say Well, this is a prison in
ничего не скажет Ну это тюрьма вот в
Mariupol at the
Мариуполе в
airport, which Well,
аэропорту кото Ну
the building was like a year ago
здание года типа было
and here in it there are reprisals against people who are
т и вот в ней расправ с людьми кото
Russian  views that is, they dealt with
российских взглядов то есть расправились
them according to Ukrainian law
по украинскому законодательству их там
somehow or what they did with them I didn't understand
как-то или что сделали с ними я не понял
Well, you can not comply with
Ну можно же не соблюдать
the law I think if it was a
законодательство Я думаю если это была
Secret how they do not comply with the law
Тайна как не соблюдают законодательство
you say that in Ukraine everyone
вы сказать то что в Украине все
complies with the law Well, yes, we have
соблюдают законодательство Ну да у нас
human rights activists  there are no problem lawyers
правозащитники есть без проблем адвокаты
defenders but I
защитники но я просто
also just watch one YouTube channel
тоже наблюдаю за одним YouTube каналом
also a person from Russia here in chat roulette
тоже человек из России вот в чат рулетке
talking and he came across a
разговаривает и ему попался
servicewoman of the
военнослужащей
ZSU who freely said that yes
зсу который свободно сказал что да нас
NATO taught us there how to behave
натовцы обучали там как нужно себя вести
with prisoners but you understand that this is
с пленными но вы же понимаете это ничего
nothing  observed accordingly Well, it means that
не соблюдается соответственно Ну значит
not everything is so sweet in Ukraine I have no idea
не всё так сладко в Украине Понятия не
about What kind of conversation is this we
имею про Какой разговор имеет вот мы
are talking about real facts and not about the
говорим про реальные факты а не про
conversations of some
разговоры каких-то
people I would like to say to finish our
людей Я бы хотел сказать закончить наш
dialogue with the fact that probably it is good Where there is
диалог тем что наверное хорошо Там где
no us and
нас нет и Рух
no Rukh  where there are none of us where there is none of me where
нет хо где нас всех нет где нет меня где
there are none of
нет
you it is possible yes for a very long time here we are engaged in
вас можно да очень долго вот заниматься
polemics but I think sooner or later
полемика но я думаю рано или поздно
each of us each of us will find Peace above our
каждый нас каждый из нас обретёт Мир над
heads Peaceful sky and each of us
головой Мирное небо и у каждого из нас
will be fine and we will not
всё будет хорошо и мы не будем
engage in such stupidity sitting
заниматься такой глупостью сидеть
try to talk  probably
разговаривать пытаться наверно кому-то
show something to someone
что-то показать на
I don't want to convince you I want to understand
Я хочу не переубедить вас я хочу понять
I want to understand
Я хочу понять
Russians and we'll just do our own
русских а будем просто заниматься своими
thing spend time with families
делами проводить время с семьями
help those who need help Everything
помогать тем кто нуждается в помощи Всё
will be fine with us thank you for this
у нас будет хорошо спасибо вам для этого
yes For this we need  withdraw troops from
да Для этого надо забрать войска из
Ukraine and everything will be fine True Well,
Украины и всё будет хорошо Правда Ну это
you will tell someone else
вы там другому кому-нибудь
I will now catch up guys
скаже я вот сейчас пой го ребят все
let's go out Well, at least you
давайте выходим Ну вы по крайней мере
will stop supporting says Yes, I
перестанете поддерживать говорит Да я
support Good day to you, see you soon,
поддерживаю Доброго дня вам до сда
happy
щаслива
yeah, that's the kind of thing the bagatyohs have  Russia,
угу вот така цикава у багатьох росия рч
here they are, they are trespassing inside But they want it
вот вони тримають вну Але вони хочуть
not to be inside, so that it is peaceful, that is, a peaceful
щоб не було вни щоб мирно то есть
sky, so that the Armed Forces would take care of
Мирного неба щоб ВС були займались
their own, everything is fine, but I find fault with
своими симя все добре але я тримаю вину
Toto in the World Cup, in what logic you if you want a
Тото в ЧМ в чму логика ты якщо хочеш
peaceful sky, then maybe you don't need to trespass
мирне небо то можливо не треба тривати
inside like that  foreign cranes It is logical that
вну так в чуж крани Це ж логично тому що
it is surprising  you see what they say that
навить дивиться нать якщо кажуть що там
Ukraine here there in short did something so
Украина десь там короче щось робила так
it's already blocked so there are victims I see they
вна вже перекрыла будя так жертви я нать
could have gotten rich there let's say
могли там нарахувати х скажем
fake faces so
фейко личики так
Toto Ukraine ditch Bomb Bomb Bomb
Тото Украина ров Бомбила Бомбила Бомбила
but not you Bomb bomb and bomb costs
да не вы Бомбила бамбас а бамбас стоить
so much and Russia took it in two months  Mariupol
так а росия за два мися зняла Мариуполь
land so harv rose Bombila so
землею так харв роз Бомбила так
and who Tod bombed 8 ditch and who if here for
и хто Тод бомби 8 ров и кого якщо тут за
two months really erased hundred z
два мися реально стерли ста
from the land of the region of the Land
з с земли обл Земли
Donetsk
Донецк
cost maybe someone deception But Naika
стоить можливо хтось обман Але Найка
When people from Ross where z blim crying is
Коли люди з рос де з блим плакати не
impossible to go out because you immediately  I'll
можна вийти тому что тебе зразу же
throw you in a paddy wagon and they'll tell you about Yas there,
загребу в автозак розказують про Ясь там
the lack of respect for people's rights in Ukraine, it's
недотримання прав людини в украини це
really funny, although it's not funny
реально весело хоча це не весело
because they have
тому що у них
the same things as
спотворений
we do  there are no rights people And in them all is
що У нас нема прав людини А в них все
good and they want to throw their model
добре и вони хочуть ось цю свою модель
on us instead of that, so that in themselves in the
накину на нас замисть того щоб в себе в
land
краи
[music]
[музыка]
to build a lawful
будувати правову
state, but half of them think about
державу ось так а полва цикаво думку зу
people,
люди
although all of them
хоча вс
know how to find their own reasons
ВС яко знаходять соб якесь обгрунтування
this letter on y Telegram right now axis
цього пись на й Telegram прям зараз ось
VN and
ВН а
pok ce very and very important YouTube is busy
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through srg or in your ban and very
нас через срг ор в твий бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali prompt connections are
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
written right now  Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegrams okrim video tezh tsikava and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we are obliged to you
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
trimati constant operational connections
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that chi  I'll show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
subscribe and
подпишись а